<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Conference name</title>
    <link>https://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Conference name</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/cfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/cfp/</guid>
      <description>Call for papers In recent years we witnessed a growing interest towards leveraging Artificial Intelligence (AI) tools to innovate network operations at all layers, domains and planes. Yet, if, what and where we need to integrate intelligence in networks and how to (re)design networks for the native support of AI is still largely under debate. This is due to the multi-faceted nature of the challenges behind such integration: on the one hand, network architectures must be updated to accommodate AI models and their lifecycle by design (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/committee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/committee/</guid>
      <description>Committee Co-chairs Alessandro Finamore Huawei Technologies, France Marco Fiore IMDEA Networks Carlee Joe-Wong Carnegie Mellon University TPC Members Albert Cabellos Universitat Politecnica de Catalunya Amedeo Sapio Intel Andra Lutu Telefonica Bo Ji Virginia Tech Chen Tian Nanjing University Chuan Wu University of Hong Kong Chuanxiong Guo Bytedance George Iosifidis Delft University of Technology Gianni Antichi Queen Mary University of London Ilias Leontiadis Meta John Chi Shing Lui Chinese University of Hong Kong Junchen Jiang University of Chicago Kyunghan Lee Seoul National university Marco Canini King Abdullah University of Science and Technology Marco Gramaglia Universidad Carlos III de Madrid Roberto González NEC Laboratories Europe Tao Han New Jersey Institute of Technology Tian Lan George Washington University Vaneet Aggarwal Purdue University Xiaoxi Zhang Sun Yat-Sen University Zied Ben Houidi Huawei Technologies France Zinan Lin Carnegie Mellon University </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/contacts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/contacts/</guid>
      <description>Contacts For any questions please reach out to the chairs Alessandro Finamore, Marco Fiore and Carlee Joe-Wong</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/dates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/dates/</guid>
      <description>Deadlines Abstract registration September 23rd, 2022 Submission September 30th, 2022 Extended Submission October 3rd, 2022 (11:59pm AoE) Notification October 21st, 2022 Camera ready November 1st, 2022 (hard deadline) Workshop Event December 9th, 2022 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/submission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/submission/</guid>
      <description>Submission instructions Authors should submit only original work that has not been published before and is no under submission to any other venue.
All submitted papers will be assessed through a double-blind review process. This means that the authors do not see who are the reviewers and the reviewers do not see who are the authors.
As an author, you should do your best to ensure that your paper submission does not directly or indirectly reveal the authors&amp;rsquo; identities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
